Hey, slow down, Mike.
Okay? You're making me sick.
I would slow down if you hadn't
already made us late.
W-We're not late, okay?
You're just anxious.
No, I'm anxious
'cause you made us late.
And I'm not doing this with you
in the next phase of our lives.
You're gonna respect my time.
My stomach. My stomach.
Hey, Mike, look.
Pull over at that store
right there.
I need a ginger ale.
Look, we don't have no time
to get no ginger ale, man.
Come on, Mike, I'm sick.
You're freaking me out, okay?
-I feel like I'm gonna throw...
-throw up.
I dare you, Marcus.
You got 90 seconds, all right?
Ginger ale and nothing else.
I am a grown-ass man.
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay? Just be nice.
Oh, okay. 85 seconds.
Ooh-ooh!
Are those dogs fresh?
I put 'em on yesterday.
Well, give me one
and, uh, put some relish
and some mustard
on that motherfucker.
Hook it up. Come on, hurry up.
Yeah, no, that one right there.
Yeah. Yeah, that right there.
Hurry up.
Got to go, got to go.
Don't be taking your time.
Yeah, my man. Oh.
Hey, open the register.
-No, no, no.
-Now!
Sir, today is not the day.
Shut the fuck up!
Look, if I'm not in that car
in 15 seconds...
there's a very surly man
that's coming in here,
and we both are fucked.
-Marcus.
-Hey, don't fucking move!
Get the fuck over there!
Hey, Mike,
I told this guy I had to go.
Mm-mm. Is that Skittles
on the counter, Marcus?
Well, he was taking a long time
w-with the ginger ale.
That is incorrect.
He grabbed that ginger ale
the second he came in here.
A hot dog, Marcus?
You're not supposed to be
eating that shit.
-This is not mine, Mike.
-Yes, it is.
Mind your business
with your tattletaling ass.
Everybody, shut the fuck up!
Sir, I'm gonna need you
to lower your weapon.
Come take my weapon, then,
motherfucker.
Don't antagonize him.
Marcus, get in the car.
Mike, he has a gun to my head.
Want to deal with him
or you want to deal with me?
Sorry, sir, but I got to go.
You didn't
have to shoot him, Mike.
Get in the car.
Call 911.
Aren't you the police?
Other people look at you
and see the tailored suits,
the cars, the watches.
I met you without any of that--
stripped, basically naked--
which is 90% of why
I'm marrying you.
I met you at your lowest.
You'd been shot.
But there was a fire in you
that was extraordinary.
And I vow to spend the rest
of my life fanning that flame.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Yes.
You know,
it kind of makes sense
that he married his therapist
after he got shot.
-I love that for him.
-Mm-hmm.
Mental health
is super important.
Well, it was
his physical therapist.
Congratulations, Michael.
Rita. Thank you, thank you.
Mr. Mayor.
Oh, not yet. Don't jinx it.
I'm still just a lowly
U.S. Attorney.
Uh, I've been watching
what you're doing.
-You got my vote.
-Aw, thank you.
Congratulations to you.
-Well...
-I mean,
the definition of
a power couple right there.
-I'll, uh, grab you a drink.
-Okay.
Can I get you anything?
No, I'm good. Thank you.
And all this time, I thought
you were a terminal bachelor.
I-I, uh...
I even surprised myself
with this one.
Yeah, I guess you just hadn't
met the right one.
I had some growing up to do.
You were 50.
Uh...
Whew.
Okay, uh...
I'm gonna pre-apologize
for whatever he says.
Uh-uh.
-Mike.
-Uh-uh-uh. Don't sta...
-No.
-Marcus.
-You know how it is.
-Marcus. Come...
-Let me get it out.
Come on, man.
-Everything you done
been through, man. -Okay.
The witch, the Bruja.
The prostitute.
My sister.
Remember? You could've told me
about my sister, Mike.
You could've told me that.
I would've embraced you
if that's who she was feeling.
-I love you, Mike.
-No doubt.
You know, Cap would've loved
to been here to see this.
But you know what,
we got his daughter Judy
and his granddaughter Callie.
She wants to say something.
Um, my granddad loved you guys,
and if he were here,
he would've told you
not to eff this up.
That's what he would've said.
Yeah, he would've said,
"Don't fuck it up." Oh!
Exactly.
Oh, excuse... excuse me.
Hey.
Mike, you been my partner
a long time.
Yes, sir.
Now he's gonna be
your partner, Christine.
To Mike and Christine Lowrey...
-for life!
-For life!
Go, Marcus!
What happened? What happened?
Marcus. Marcus!
-Sir, what's the address?
-Let me in. Let me in.
-Let me in. Let me in. Back up!
-What's the address?
This is Captain Rita Secada.
I have an officer
in cardiac arrest.
Come on, man.
It's not your time.
Marcus!
Marc...
This guy.
Hey, buddy.
What you doing?
I spent my whole life
being scared, Mike.
I wasted so much time.
Wh-Why don't you, uh...
why don't you just, uh,
step back from the edge
a little bit, please.
What year is it?
It's Tuesday.
Same year your ass
was wobbling in.
Oh, wow.
Felt like it was five years.
I was in the basement
of the ocean.
All my bullshit was gone.
Just freedom.
And full-body love, Mike.
-Full-body love.
-All right. Okay.
Wh-Why-Why don't you, uh,
love your full body back
from the-the ledge, please?
Nothing to be scared of.
It's not my time, baby.
It's not my time.
Mr. Burnett!
Uh, uh, hey, uh, I got him.
He-he-he's just, um...
I don't know
what the fuck he's doing.
Uh, but I got it.
I-I got him.
We're good. We are good.
-We are great!
-Hey.
-Miami!
-Whoa.
305 for life!
Kakow!
-All right, just...
-Kakow!
You gonna put somebody's
eye out with that thing, man.
I'm bringing the thunder, Mike.
-I get it.
-Bringing the thunder.
Yeah, all right. There you go.
Oh, man.
Bring it in.
Thought I lost you, brother.
Couldn't lose me if you tried.
You know your ass is out,
right?
Everybody's ass is out, Mike.
Hey.
There's a storm coming.
No, not that kind of storm.
You're gonna be tested.
Things are gonna get bad,
and you're gonna have to make
a really hard choice.
Just know you're good.
This is my private time,
Mr. McGrath.
How may I help you?
I need you to move some money.
-Your money?
-Your boss's, actually.
I need it to be cartel cash.
Just under 20 million.
Backdated series of transfers--
beginning 2004,
ending January 2020--
into that account
in the name of the late
Captain Conrad Howard.
I have people
who can handle logistics.
I really just need
your log-in credentials.
And why would I give you those?
Oh, my God!
Shh.
Come here, darling.
Come on.
Come here.
You can't transfer funds
from a phone.
Hey, honey. What's going on?
Do... do...
do they know each other?
Honey, who's there with you?
-All right, all right.
-Honey...
Here we go.
They'll kill you for this.
They're not even gonna know
this happened.
Your girlfriend heard you
on the phone with your wife
and realized you were never
gonna divorce her.
And in a fit of passion,
she shot you.
Your bodyguard tried
to step in,
but he was too late.
And realizing the horror
of her actions...
-...she took her own life.
-No!
Honey, what are you doing?
-You had a heart attack
two weeks ago. -Exactly.
They call it a widow-maker
for a reason.
You need to be
in the hospital, baby.
Hey, I tried to...
Told his ass, T.
He... Yeah, uh,
apparently, he's an adult.
He was allowed
to sign hisself out.
Hey, babe, look.
Come on. I couldn't take
one more second away from you.
All these stents in me
got my blood flowing.
I'm on "D" way.
All right, now.
Oh, hey, hey.
Come on, man. That's my phone.
-I love you, Marcus.
-We'll be there in ten.
All right, babe.
All right. Love you.
Hey, Mike, I wasn't even
gonna tell you this,
but this ain't
the first time we done this.
We ride together all the time.
What you mean?
No, I'm talking about
our souls.
You know,
we've ridden together,
but I saw it all, Mike.
We're bound, and we have been
for lifetimes.
We haven't always been
Mike and Marcus,
but we've always been us.
Um...
What you talking about?
We're soulmates.
-Yep.
-Yeah.
Nah.
Yeah, I kind of...
I-I saw my soulmate looking
a little different than that.
See, see, see, Mike,
you stuck in the physical.
Souls don't have dicks.
I'm pretty sure my soul
has a dick, Marcus.
See?
That's that shit right there.
That's why we're stuck.
You know, I wasn't gonna
tell you this shit, either...
-Mm-hmm.
-...but, uh, my soul is
more advanced than your soul.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
It's not that your soul
is stupid.
-Mm-hmm.
-You know?
It's just that
you're more like a...
-a baby soul, you know?
-Mm-hmm.
And I'm more like
a mother soul.
-Mm-hmm.
-And I just got to suckle you.
You know?
-Put you on that titty, okay?
-Oh, yeah.
You know?
Hey, how long you think
your brain went without oxygen?
Daddy's home.
-Where my family?
-Honey, you're back.
-My family.
-Oh, baby.
-Hey, baby.
-Hey.
-Look. Granddaddy.
-Oh! Little Marcus!
Say hi to Pop-Pop.
-Hi.
-Say hi to Granddad.
-Yes.
-Aw. I missed you so...
-Look at you, woman.
-Look at...
-No, come on. Look at me, baby.
-Mm, mm.
We're gonna
have to hose them down.
All right.
All right, we get it.
We get it.
Put some ice in your drawers
or something.
Aw, that's funny.
Are you feeling good, Marcus?
I never felt better in my life.
Oh, Marcus.
I missed you so much, honey,
but you need to get some rest.
Oh, no, baby. I need you.
Just let me get
some electrolytes.
-Okay, baby. Give me a kiss.
-All right.
So, what's going on
with my dad?
Um, well, he-he was
on the roof, uh, naked.
And, uh, he said he had been
at the basement of the ocean.
"Amazing Chickpeas"?
Uh, oh, and he said, uh,
I have a stupid baby soul
-with no penis.
-Hmm. Mm.
Hey, Reggie!
-Yes, sir.
-Did you eat my snacks?
No... no, sir.
I was looking forward
to my snacks, Reggie.
-Honey.
-Ah...
You know what?
You need to get a job.
I'm a U.S. Marine, sir.
Well, then you need to deploy.
We just got back from Yemen.
Thank you for your service.
-You thought I was dead,
didn't you? -Dead?
One thing you don't know,
Reggie:
I got a camera up in here.
Yeah.
Theresa!
It's the doctor's orders,
Marcus.
You're on a strict diet:
no salt, no sugar, no fats.
No stress, no loud noises,
no physical exertion.
Just sit your ass down
somewhere, man.
Tell him, Mike.
And, honey,
I'm doing it with you.
We're now vegetarians.
Vegetarians? Look at me.
Look at all this man, baby.
I'm brand-new.
I need animal sugars
to survive.
Well, baby,
I have a salad for you.
-A salad?
-Hey.
Uh, T, looks like
you got this under control.
Uh, my tour of duty is done.
Bye, Christine. Bye, Mike.
-Bye, guys.
-H-Hey, Mike.
Wait up. Wait up, wait up.
-Yeah, yeah.
-What you about to do?
Can you run a quick-quick
for me?
What... Yeah, what you need?
Um, I'll give you a thousand
dollars for some Skittles.
Marcus, I am not buying
your ass no candy, man.
Okay. 2,000, Mike,
for some Ding Dongs.
And that's my final offer.
I think you're gonna be
Ding Dong-less.
Like my soul.
You always take whoever I love.
This is Detective Mike Lowrey.
Captain is down.
He's my son.
You got
a fucked-up family, Mike.
Department of Justice
has been investigating
the corruption
in the Miami Police Department,
and we now have
credible intelligence
that Captain Conrad Howard
was directing these elements
in coordination
with the cartels.
No, I'm not interested
in approximately what time.
I need to know
exactly what time.
Do you understand?
You knew about this?
I found out two weeks ago.
A press conference? Really?
I'm sorry about the way
you had to find out,
but given your closeness...
Our closeness?
Neither one of y'all
would have a job
if it wasn't for
Captain Howard.
Rita, you know
this is not true.
Honestly, I don't.
The investigation
has turned up new evidence.
Miami law enforcement's been
a leaky ship for years now.
Witnesses turn up dead.
Informants disappear.
Events appear random
until you aggregate them
over a period of years.
Then a pattern emerges.
Who is this?
Bud Grice, FBI, heading up
the JTF on this show.
That's who I am.
Now, we knew someone was
providing intelligence
to a cartel moving product
into South Florida.
We just didn't know who.
A cartel banker turned up dead
two weeks ago,
shot by his girlfriend.
They found a phone
with Howard's contact on it.
Years of communication
with the cartel,
account references offshore.
Millions in Howard's name.
Final piece we needed to nail
that dirty motherfucker.
-Grice.
-Oh, whoa.
Hey, hey. Let me holla at you.
Um, you know I was with him
when he went down, right?
Call him dirty one more time.
I dare you.
We know he had others
who were with him.
We're gonna find them, too.
I was with him.
Put the cuffs on me right now.
-I was with him.
-Mike.
No, these motherfuckers think
that just 'cause he's dead
and can't defend hisself,
they gonna dump all this shit
on him, burn his legacy.
Not on my watch.
This is Judy Howard,
U.S. Marshals.
I realize I have
no jurisdiction here,
but as a professional courtesy,
I'd like to request visibility
into the sources of the
allegations against my father.
Judy.
We're gonna figure
this shit out, all right?
How's Callie?
How do you think, Mike?
We're on the same team here,
Judy.
Like hell we are, Mike.
My dad would still be alive
if it weren't for
-your bastard son.
-Judy.
If I ever catch him
out on the street,
I swear on my father
I will put him down.
Come on. Come on, man. Come on.
So, what's our next move?
They said he was working
with the cartel.
Let's ask the cartel.
How you doing?
It's prison.
Yeah.
Look, we need your help.
They're saying that
Captain Howard was dirty.
Do you know anything
about that?
How much time I get off
for this one?
I'm still working on that.
This is me telling you
that I need you.
Mm.
I need to know
if Captain Howard
was working with the cartels.
No.
He was onto the ones that were.
So he got green-lit.
Wait, no.
No, Captain Howard was killed
because he was on
your mother's hit list.
He was added to it.
Your people wanted it
to look like us.
Your people wanted him dead.
What you mean "our people"?
You should be careful.
You're playing a game when
you don't even know the rules.
There's dirty players
on your side.
-That's bullshit.
-Wait, who?
I saw him one time.
-Can you I.D. him?
-Sí.
Give me a name.
I don't know his name.
My mother.
She's the one
who dealt with him.
I knew we should've
kept that damn witch alive.
Marcus.
May she rest in peace.
Dude.
Hey, boss.
Our man on the inside
got all of Howard's records
in the JTF file.
Computers, phones,
files, all of it.
Well, we know Howard
was onto our operation.
We just don't know
how much he had.
We need to make sure
we got every trace.
That's beautiful.
Hey, boss.
It's all the paper files.
They're clean so far.
Two phones had nothing.
His office computer was empty.
-He was careful.
-But?
But his old personal laptop
had weak encryption.
Here... we go.
Shit.
We tripped a fail-safe.
The fuck you mean, "we"?
Something was sent.
To who?
Tracing the phone now.
What the hell?
He's texting us
from the other side.
No, he's not, Marcus.
If you're seeing this,
I'm probably dead.
Fuck. Fuck me.
Before I begin,
I want to say one thing:
I'm putting you
in mortal danger.
Boys, we got rats in our walls.
But I-I got to make sure
you're my bad boys.
The Coke bottle giant
is the key.
What?
Don't trust anybody.
What's that?
What does that mean?
"The Coke bottle giant."
Fletcher.
Oh, shit.
These are the guys.
We should put a bullet
in these motherfuckers.
Be done with it
once and for all.
Lintz, I love you.
I'd like nothing more
than to let you loose on them,
but extra dead cops
doesn't do us any favors here.
Keep them
under constant surveillance
and see if they make a move.
Fletcher's warehouse
is right down that alley.
Mike, I wasn't even gonna
tell you this...
Ugh. Then don't tell me.
No, you got to hear this.
This is big.
I can't die.
What?
I cannot die.
Motherfucker, you did
a pretty good job of dying
at my wedding
a couple weeks ago.
But I didn't.
Watch.
Hey, Marcus.
Hey!
Hey! Marcus! Marcus!
Hey, stop, stop. Hey. Hey!
Marcus!
What are you,
some kind of moron?
Stop, stop.
Please stop!
-Hey!
-Bro!
Slow down!
Crosswalk!
Ah...
Talk to me.
-You got to trust, Mike.
-Mm-hmm.
Trust yourself.
Trust the universe.
Stop that shit, Marcus.
It's not my time, Mike.
Oh, okay, so you're saying
that if I shoot you
in your face,
you're saying
that you won't die?
Fate dictates that you won't
shoot me in the face.
I'm saying...
I'm-I'm saying that you saying
that if I shoot you
in your face,
are you saying you won't die?
Fate doesn't deal
in hypotheticals, Mike.
¡Oye! ¿Qué estás haciendo?
I'm going to call the police!
They're already here, ma'am.
Mind your business.
Just go to the beach.
Stop that shit, Marcus.
See? You're putting
your gun away.
He's putting his gun away.
Ooh. Mike.
Focus, man.
Yeah, I call this place,
you know,
Creative Space for
Black Imagination, you know.
-That's...
-Fletcher.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
What the hell is this place?
This is my studio gallery.
I'm an artiste now.
Please, you ain't
no damn artist.
-What do you guys want?
-Captain Howard.
Yeah, I was sorry to hear
what happened to him.
He helped turn my life around.
He told us to talk to you.
Okay. Talk to me.
I just talked to you.
Then say what
you're supposed to say.
-I said what I'm supposed
to say. -You didn't.
Then tell me what
I'm supposed to say.
I've said all I can say.
You fucking with us, beanstalk.
Marcus!
Come on.
Captain Howard saved my life.
I'm not messing this up.
I can't say
what I supposed to say
until you say
what you supposed to say.
Fletcher, just tell us
what you supposed to tell us.
Dumbasses. Look.
Captain Howard
was onto something big.
He didn't trust that you
dumb fucks would figure it out,
so he contacted me.
Because you're stupid
and I'm a genius.
So I protected the information
in something.
In something beautiful.
Flex your face one more time.
Flex it again!
I will blow
your fucking head off.
Would you stop? Come on.
In something
that will live forever.
Did you shoot him?
I don't think so.
Freeze!
Marcus. Marcus!
You hit?
Nah. Black jelly bean.
Nobody likes that shit.
Whoa.
Hey! Stop that stupid shit!
I'm not fucking with you! Stop!
No! No, no!
No! No!
I don't give a fuck!
Marcus, stop! No!
-What are you doing?!
-I got this!
But you don't, though!
No. No!
Marcus!
Let's go! Let's move!
Burnett and Lowrey
are moving north on 11th.
Miami PD! Go!
What are you doing?!
I'm fighting crime, baby.
Freeze!
Mike!
Have you ever had
a panic attack before?
What?
Ain't nobody have
no damn panic attack.
You're at 165 over 90.
Sweaty, nauseous.
Look, there's no shame
in getting counseling.
-All right. Thank you.
-Mike.
Appreciate you, brother.
Mike, let the man do his job.
-What...
-Okay.
Good... good job, man.
Hey, Mike.
What the hell
you panicking about?
I'm not speaking to you.
What'd I do?
You two all right?
Mike had a panic attack.
He didn't. Mike is fine.
What happened?
Rita, you ain't gonna
believe this shit,
-but we got a text from...
-A tip.
We got a tip that Fletcher
had violated his parole,
so we came down here, and...
obviously, he was into some
shit he ain't have no business.
Is that true, Marcus?
Uh, um...
You know, well, you know, I...
I was with Mike.
How could you, of all people,
think Captain Howard was dirty?
I don't want this to be true,
but it would benefit all of us
to do our jobs
and follow the evidence.
And you think
he was stupid enough
to put accounts
in his own name?
-He's being framed.
-By who?
That's what we're trying
to find out.
Rita, come on,
you're smarter than this.
Michael, please do not forget
you're talking to your boss.
I'm trying to protect you here.
I got no footage
for a two-block radius.
What?
They must have killed all CCTV,
all security cams.
I got nothing.
At least they ain't
film your panic attack.
Hey, guys.
-You had a panic attack?
-No.
If you want, I can recommend
a good counselor.
I'm good, Dorn. Thanks.
Look, I shot this,
went frame by frame.
Check it out.
All right, not here.
-Dorn, shut it down.
-Yeah.
Hey. Let's go.
So, what is this?
We're not exactly sure.
-Whoa.
-Wow.
There you go. There you go.
All right, you fucks.
Now that I know it's you,
here it is.
I don't know how high up
it goes,
but there's corrupt officials
on our side,
and they're working
with the cartel.
This all started smelling funny
about nine years ago.
That shipment of coke we were
about to raid went missing.
You know, I-I kept getting
shut down from above.
So I... I pulled Sanchez
and Ruiz out of retirement.
I had 'em working
on the outside, you know?
They were killed in a car crash
a week later.
That shook me up.
And it's why I never
brought you two in.
Well, shame on me for worrying
about your asses
when you could've saved mine.
But now it's up to you.
Remember the bust back in 2003?
314 pounds of ecstasy?
Well, I held on to the
storage unit, off the books.
That's where
the real files are.
Everything you need
to exterminate
these rat fucks, it's in there.
You're gonna have to finish
what I couldn't.
Please.
Please, boys.
You're my last hope.
2003, um...
that was the-the Haitian,
Zoe Pound.
Where was their storage locker?
I have no idea. All right.
We need you guys to go down
to the station
and pull
our original case files.
That'll tell us
where the locker is.
Do it quietly and be careful.
We don't know who we can trust.
Shit, this is heavy, man.
Um...
I just got something
important to say.
I'm just gonna come out
with it, clear the air.
Uh, the rat is not me, so...
Thanks for that, Dorn.
I feel safer.
They just tried to kill my son
because Armando can prove that
Captain Howard was innocent.
Cap was onto
these dirty players.
Armando told you that?
Yes. It's the reason they
wanted Captain Howard dead.
Armando can I.D. the guy
that ordered the hit on Cap.
He have a name?
No.
But a face.
Listen, I know y'all
can do this, all right?
Just transfer Armando.
Get him to Miami.
Get him to a secure location.
We'll-we'll debrief him.
We'll get his testimony.
We'll get some pictures
in front of him.
But please do it now.
These guys are trying
to cover their asses,
and they are not gonna stop.
Do it for Captain Howard.
Look, the evidence
against Captain Howard
is overwhelming.
If I'm doing this,
I'm doing it for you.
All right.
Let's transfer Aretas.
You'll accompany him,
get him to igloo here in Miami,
do a debrief.
But I'm sticking my neck out
and I'm trusting you.
If he turns out to be bullshit,
then it's gonna be my ass.
So... don't screw me, Mike.
All right.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yeah?
We found
Zoe Pound's storage unit.
We'll go get the files,
then take them
to my houseboat
for safekeeping.
All right. Stay on it.
Let me know when you got it.
Please surrender your firearms.
They will be returned to you
upon touchdown.
You good?
Never been better.
It's about 45 minutes.
Mike, I wasn't even
gonna tell you this,
but in one of our previous
lifetimes together...
Mm-hmm?
...you were a donkey,
and I owned you.
You were a stubborn ass, Mike.
-Mm-hmm.
-You used to bite and spit.
-You were nasty.
-Mm-hmm.
But I-I was a terrible owner,
you know,
-because I used to beat you.
-Mm-hmm.
Because you wouldn't
listen for shit.
And maybe I beat some kind
of shame into you, Mike.
And now I realize
I was scarring your soul.
You miss your nap?
Mike, I'm trying
to apologize to you.
We don't have your blankie,
but you could just
rest your eyes.
That's exactly how you was
as a donkey.
-Okay. I get it.
-That's that shit there.
You need some help
with your seat belt?
No, donkey.
Hey.
Bryant, this is Bronson.
The other guys
are on turnaround.
Take a seat.
What's up?
Read the lines.
"U.S. Marshal flight 724.
"We have an emergency.
"Our prisoner
has escaped custody
"with the aid of Miami PD--
Lowrey and Burnett.
"There are officers down.
"Mayday. Mayday. They are
coming for the cockpit.
"I repeat,
"they are hijacking the CH-47.
All ground units,
please respond."
-Give me Lowrey's gun.
-Copy.
Go, go! Get Lowrey.
Let's go!
We welcome the storm,
motherfuck...
Get me out
of this fucking cage!
Marcus!
Mike!
-It's too heavy!
-Don't let go!
Grab the stick!
Where the hell
you learn how to fly?
I'm a drug dealer, man.
To the right!
He was using my gun.
How the hell did they get
on a federal transport?
We need to split up.
We're gonna stay together.
Says who?
I'm not asking you.
I'm telling you.
We're staying together.
-Fuck out of my way.
-Hey. Where...
-Hey! Hey!
-Get the fuck off me.
-Listen!
Look, you are the only person
who can identify
whoever is doing this.
The only way that
any of us stays alive
is if we get them
before they get us.
There's no us. There is no us!
Damn.
That Lowrey DNA is a bitch.
Y'all some
strong motherfuckers.
Okay. Now, look,
everybody unflex on three.
One. Two.
There you go.
Captain Howard left us files
that's gonna tell us
who's doing this.
Dorn has them.
We just have to get back
to Miami.
You better not slow me down.
Lose your phones.
You keep up with me,
or I leave you in the dirt.
You're in my world now.
Hey, Mike.
Look, we got to think
about this.
I know you want to move
with him,
you know,
because he's your "son."
Whoa. Whoa.
Don't air-quote that.
No, I-I didn't. I'm just saying
I know why you trying
to protect him--
'cause he "family."
Hey.
Moving the air quotes
down to your hips
doesn't un-air-quote them.
Just-just say he's my son.
-He's your son.
-No, no.
Palms up is like
you trying to say,
oh, he's not really my son.
Oh.
Well, your son's getting away.
Shit.
If your men
are on some kind of op,
you might want to pull us in.
Otherwise, it doesn't
look good for them.
Yeah.
-Judy.
-You I.D. the bodies?
Roger.
We got three unaccounted for:
Lowrey, Burnett and Aretas.
Motherfuckers.
Fucking... Shit.
All right. Listen up!
We have three suspects,
armed and dangerous, out there.
And I want them back.
Let's go.
Hold on. Judy.
Three suspects?
What do you think
is happening here?
Wh-What do you think?
Play the audio.
U.S. Marshal flight 724.
We have an emergency.
Our prisoner
has escaped custody
with the aid of Miami PD--
Lowrey and Burnett.
There are officers down.
Mayday. Mayday.
Come on, you can't
possibly believe
Mike and Marcus would do this.
Nah, you said it.
Lowrey was obsessed with
getting his son out of prison.
Slow down, Judy.
This isn't Miami, Secada.
These are my fugitives,
and right now the whole world
is my jurisdiction.
You've known them
your whole life.
How can you even suggest...
Do I think that
Mike and Marcus planned this?
Probably not.
But people do things
they wouldn't normally do
when family's involved.
In my experience,
innocent men don't run.
Can we stop and think before...
Are you capable
of doing your job?
'Cause I need to move on.
They survived.
The fuck you mean,
they survived?
No bodies on site.
U.S. Marshals are treating it
as a manhunt.
These guys just refuse to die.
They're wanted men.
Law enforcement
and media are our friends now.
A manhunt for three fugitives
is sending shock waves
across South Florida.
Ballistic reports
have matched the bullets
recovered from
the bodies at the...
Are you planning
on dropping out
of the mayor's race
in light of the recent events?
The manhunt
is currently underway.
The FBI is assisting
U.S. Marshals
in bringing these men in.
Lowrey, Burnett and Aretas
should be considered
armed and dangerous.
These are individuals
who have killed
fellow law enforcement
professionals.
If you see something,
say something.
Put a bounty on the streets.
Get it
to every gang in the city
and let them fight for it.
Five mil.
Let's go get
these motherfuckers.
The universe
is crazy, ain't it?
Look at us.
I bet none of us thought
when we woke up today
this is where we'd be.
You out of jail.
We going to jail.
This shit is special.
Mike, is there anything you
would like to say to Armando?
Fuck you talking to me
like that? No.
Mike, this is a moment.
Express with your son.
I'm sorry.
That's what I'm talk...
That's what I'm talking...
For what?
For everything, man.
Seems like bad shit happens
to anybody I love, so...
starting to think
maybe I'm cursed.
I just feel like...
maybe I cursed you.
You ain't fucking curse me.
Bad shit happens to everybody.
Ain't always about you.
Hey, Armando.
I don't know
if I told you this,
but I died
a couple of weeks ago.
-Sorry to hear about that.
-Oh, no.
Best thing
that ever happened to me.
Shit's wild.
But y'all...
y'all the reason I came back.
Hey.
Everybody, bring it in.
Come on, bring it in.
Come on.
-Dude.
-Bring...
There you go, Armando.
There you go. There you...
Y'all are some terrible
fucking fugitives.
So, what-what are you,
fucking Marcus Winfrey?
-What?
-What you... See?
-I'm just trying...
-You making us look soft,
like we don't know
how to be on the run.
We got to get you out of this.
Hey.
That boy hardheaded.
Chip off the old block.
Well, what we got here?
Hey, Cain, come take
a look at this!
What are you boys doing?
"Boys"?
Are y'all stealing our clothes?
Looks like it.
Fucking racism.
Y'all think
just because we Black
we stealing your shit?
Now, these are
my own Black clothes
that I put on today
from my own Black closet.
-Marcus.
-What?
Look at your shirt.
Hey, man.
How'd this get
in my Black closet?
Why don't you boys sing us
a little Reba song?
-Uh, Reba?
-Reba?
Oh, yeah.
-Oh, please.
-Uh... which...
That's, um, 'cause he put...
he put me on to...
Whi-Which one?
Which y'all... Which one?
Sing your favorite.
Oh, she got plenty
of them, um...
-'Cause she got hits.
-Yeah, she got hits.
-Was it the up-tempo song?
-Yeah, yeah, remember the one?
You know, where she...
or the...
-or-or the slow jam?
-Uh...
-It was the slow one, man.
-Oh, okay, uh...
You hurt me...
Yes, 'cause she was hurt.
She was, yeah, uh...
Yes, yes.
I'm a...
-I'm a woman.
-I'm a strong Black wo...
-A strong...
Woman, yeah, 'cause
-she not Black, but...
-Yeah, she... But...
Yeah. And, um, um...
Mm-mm. Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
That ain't no Reba song.
It's from her mixtape.
Goddamn it!
We're sorry!
We'll bring it back!
We're not stealing your shit
because we Black!
Did you ever love her?
What?
My mother. You ever love her?
He's expressing.
I definitely loved her.
And then you sold her out.
I made some mistakes.
Like me.
Now, you know that is not
what I was trying...
Now, wait a damn minute,
Armando.
He's trying to make up for it.
He don't owe you a damn thing.
All right, ho-hold on.
Hold on, Marcus.
You're-you're just...
you're being aggressive.
I've been a dad a long time.
He needs to hear this, Mike.
He needs some tough-ass love.
Armando, maybe he does
owe you something, okay?
Your mom being deceived by him,
you being born in prison,
in a web of lies
that turned your ass into
a stone-cold fucking killer.
Yeah. You're a killer.
But this man, through it all,
has been nothing but solid.
That's some father-of-the-year
shit right there.
-Is it?
-Yeah.
Your wack-ass parenting
broke the truck.
My bad.
Yeah, nah, that's dead.
We're not far from Tabitha's.
Nah, Mike.
You know that woman's crazy.
Yeah, but she likes me.
I don't think she likes you
as much as you think.
The Pony's about
two miles from here.
What's The Pony?
I need my Instagram.
I need my Friendster.
I need more sex.
I need more men in this club.
You all look beautiful.
Now, get back to work.
Mike Lowrey. Damn.
What up, Tabitha?
So y'all in trouble, huh?
Yeah, uh, we need some help.
Um...
-Well, we need some clothes.
-No shit.
-A ride and some phones.
-Mm. Yeah.
Yeah. Guns, too.
Uh, that's my son.
That's Armando.
You got you
a little Spanish son?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a long story.
Um, can you hook us up?
I mean, I got all that,
but what you gonna do for me?
What you mean?
We good for that.
You were.
But you guys
are men on the run now, so...
Well, what you need?
-What I need?
-Mm-hmm.
I need you to eat this pussy.
I'm not doing that, all right?
Whoa. Hold on, Mike.
Hold on. Think about this.
Now, you say
guns and phones, right?
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay, well, look,
-you know Mike's a married man.
-So?
So he's gonna need
some plausible deniability.
So I'm-a have you lay down
and, uh, stick out your tongue,
and you gonna
have to do the rest.
I can fuck with that.
-Oh, yeah. Go on and lay down.
-No, Marcus.
All you got to do
is close your eyes, Mike.
-No. -Ooh, I'm-a need
pictures, okay?
-You know how to take pictures,
right? -Tabitha, hey.
-What?
-We don't have a lot of time.
I need you to stop
fucking around.
Oh, I'm not fucking around.
All right. Hey, let's go.
W-Wait. Hold up.
Sit your
motherfucking ass down.
Hey, Tabitha,
what is you doing?
What is you doing?
Sit your married ass down!
You get y'all asses down, too!
-Shit.
-Everybody, sit down!
Hey, I got the bad boys
right here.
Let's get that money.
-Hey, Tab.
-Shut the fuck up.
H-Hold up. I'm confused.
You didn't want him
to licky-licky?
There's a $5 million bounty
on your head.
I need that money.
I was just stalling.
That's-that's cold.
He almost did that shit.
He did not, Marcus.
-I told you she didn't
like you. -
Get the fuck up.
The bounty is dead or alive.
Don't be stupid.
Hey, Armando.
If you live,
I'll let you...
What?
I said, if you live,
motherfucker, holla at me!
He was kind of cute.
Nah.
We got a tip.
Positive I.D. on our fugitives.
Let's do this.
Ooh. Mike, I'm about
to make my move.
Oh, no, the fuck you're not.
You 'bout to go wherever
these men are taking us.
Oh, I'm not going.
Now, I'll take
the three in the front.
You take the six in the back.
Marcus, we do not have
any weapons.
-In five, four, three...
-Marcus.
Ah, shit. This motherfucker.
Hey, yo, Mike.
Ain't no fun when the rabbit
got the gun, huh?
Wait, you know this guy?
Yeah, I hit him with a hammer
a couple years ago.
You think I forgot about
that fucking ho shit
you pulled off
at Manny's Prime Rib?
How the fuck did I let
you two catch me?
Mike, I want my five million.
Marcus!
You see I got the fam with me--
the streets!
We can do this nice and easy
or we can go to war.
'Cause I'm fucking war-ready!
What are you doing?
No!
Go, go, go, go!
Back up! Back up! Back up!
No! No!
Windshield wiper fluid
is flammable!
How the hell am I supposed
to know that?
I ain't no damn scientist.
Everybody, relax.
The fire's on the outside.
Oh, shit.
Now it's on the inside.
Shit! Okay.
Okay.
Shit!
Everybody, out! Everybody, out!
Shit.
Open the damn door!
We can feel you right
there, boy. Open the door.
Shit.
Hey.
-Open up, Muscle Milk.
-Come on, man.
-What the fuck is you doing?
-Nothing.
It's just not a great time
for me right now, guys.
It's not a great time
for us, either.
Okay, let's reconvene
in like an hour or so.
Babe, we're out of body wash.
-Whoa...
-Whoa! What the hell?
We found you guys.
We're in a relationship, okay?
-Oh, okay.
-All right, yeah, that's...
Sneaking around
has been destroying me.
It started
about a couple months ago.
It will not affect
our professional lives.
Except for that one time
in that van.
-I am not sorry.
-Nothing to be sorry about.
Yeah, you know,
I-I mean, people do that shit.
Are you guys okay?
-Yeah, we're good.
-Oh.
What the fuck?
Okay. Whoa, whoa.
Hey, Kelly, Kelly.
I asked you to wait outside
for a second.
All right. Kelly, he's with us.
He can't be here.
This is my son Armando.
I know who he is, and
that's why he can't be here.
I trust you with my life, Mike,
but I sure as shit
don't trust him.
I trust him.
Then take him to your house.
Hey, Mike.
Uh, can I have a second
with her?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. Please.
-Okay. Hey, sweetie.
Relax. Relax.
Come here for a sec.
Come over here for a sec.
I asked you to wait outside.
We could both end up in jail.
Why don't we
give them a chance?
Yeah, give them a chance
to kill us all? Hmm?
This is
some dysfunctional shit.
-She's fine.
-All right.
-She don't look fine.
-I'm fine.
Yes, you are.
-Hey. All right.
-The fuck you say?
-All right. All right.
-It's the language barrier.
It was English.
-Uh...
-It was definitely English.
Thanks for the drip.
Yeah.
Okay, we're aggregating
all the data.
There's over a hundred hours
of video, 200 units of audio.
We're indexing all audio, video
and geo-located IP network data
to create a sight picture
and develop a target package.
Basically, you-you sifting
through all this shit to find
-the guilty motherfucker.
-Bingo.
Hey, Dorn.
-Yeah. -Can you safely get me
into my Ring app?
-Yeah.
-I want to see my family.
Yeah, we got
our own VPN and router.
-Uh, what's your username?
-Marcus37.
And password?
Snickers89.
Almost home, baby.
Hey, let's get to work.
We got a lot
to get through here.
So, what exactly
are we looking for?
We're looking for the guy
who ordered the hit on Cap.
Armando can I.D. him.
This fucking bastard
has been my white whale.
For the last nine years,
I've been trying
to harpoon the son of a bitch.
But now it's up to you.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Do I walk into your house and
show you how to make cocaine?
Blow it up.
It's him.
You sure?
That's the guy
that ordered the hit.
Bam. Got a name.
James McGrath.
Army Ranger School,
counterintelligence.
Deployed in Mexico until 2005.
Worked with the DEA,
Defense Attaché's Office.
Oh, shit.
He was taken hostage by...
your friends, the cartel.
Gave up his entire squad
"under duress."
It's called torture, man.
He was the only survivor.
Cap had him the whole time.
-Yeah.
-He just didn't know it.
Hey.
Hello.
Hey. It's me.
Damn it, Michael.
Where are you?
Rita, we're coming in.
We got proof that
Captain Howard is innocent.
What proof?
We got the guy
that had Captain Howard killed.
Armando I.D.'d him.
Same dude that attacked us
on the chopper:
James McGrath.
Rita, we got ten years'
worth of files.
Cap was investigating
these dudes.
We got 'em all.
It's a whole network.
We'll surrender to you
tomorrow.
Hey, look, we got to go.
Michael, what...
You okay?
Uh...
they're coming in.
What?
Michael says they have proof
that exonerates Howard,
explains everything.
Do you still love him?
What?
No.
But I believe him.
Just be careful, babe.
-Still going to dinner?
-Yeah.
They have the files.
We need to make this look like
cartel business-- Spanish only.
Shit, shit, shit!
We need some sleep.
Hey, guys, we got a problem.
Miami Central, Miami Central.
29 in progress
at 3878 Sunshine Avenue.
Oh, shit. That's my house.
Shit.
Please advise, MOS residence.
Respond forthwith.
Fuck. Fuck.
Come on, Christine.
Oh, shit.
Get a unit over to my house.
-Come on, Reggie. Pick up!
-Miami Central, we have
-another 29 in progress.
-Pick up. Pick up.
Please send units
to Detective Lowrey's
home address.
Enemy's down!
Reggie.
You got incoming.
Get the family
to somewhere safe.
-What?
-Now!
Yes, sir.
-Come on!
-Hey, what's happening?
Is anybody...
There's people
coming in the house.
-Okay.
-I got to keep y'all safe.
Come here.
-Please be careful.
-Okay, Reggie, what's happening?
-Trust me. I love you.
-Okay, honey.
Fuck. Fuck.
Behi... Behind you, Reg!
-Oh! Sh...
-Oh, damn!
Who the fuck is this guy?
That's my boy! That's my boy.
Ooh.
Damn.
Come on, come on, come on.
Ooh.
No, no, no.
-Whoa!
-Oh, shit.
Come on, come on.
-Whoo!
-Holy shit.
Oh!
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang,
motherfuckers!
Me snacks is your snacks,
Reggie!
All right, come on.
Mike, did you see that shit?
Pick up the phone.
Whoa, Mike. Mike! Mike!
One second.
-Callie.
-I saw it on TV.
My mom is after Uncle Mike.
There is no way that he did
everything that they're saying.
Sweetheart.
Everything is going to be okay.
-Okay.
-Okay?
Okay?
Hello?
It's me. Get out of the house.
I've got Callie with me.
Take her and go. Get out now!
Callie, get behind me.
Mike.
Christine!
Mr. Lowrey.
Who am I speaking to?
I think you know
who you're speaking to.
I need your boy.
And whatever evidence
your beloved captain
had squirreled away.
And for that,
you can have your wife.
I'll call you back
with instructions.
Ah, shit.
Goddamn it.
I'll go.
Let my life be worth something.
Never.
Mike.
He knew.
What do you mean?
He knew we were coming in.
He knew we had
Captain Howard's files.
He knew we had I.D.'d him.
How?
Only person you spoke to
was Rita.
It's not Rita.
Damn, she got bad taste in men.
...Justice
has been
investigating the corruption of
the Miami Police Department
with reports suggesting
the late
Captain Conrad Howard...
-Hello?
-...directed these elements
in coordination
with the cartels.
Allegations against Howard,
which look to include
Lowrey and Burnett
in the operation,
range from helping cartels
move product
into the state of Florida
as well as giving up
key witnesses,
destruction of evidence
and even the murder
of fellow officer...
-What's going on?
-I don't know.
There's been a breakthrough
in the case.
I need to get down
to the station.
I'm gonna head down there.
I'm coming with you.
Who are you texting?
Ah, just, um, just...
just got to get in touch
with the office, JTF.
Got to let everybody know.
Hey. Honey. Come on.
Honey,
what are you doing? Stop that.
What are you doing? Stop it.
-Let go of me.
-Come on. What are you doing?
Give it back to me.
Give it back!
Fuck.
Hey, hey, hey, come on.
Come on. Come on.
You okay?
Look at the phone.
You know you done
fucked up, right?
You all right?
I'm sorry.
Ain't got nothing
to be sorry for.
We'll find her, boss.
I don't trust anybody
that's not standing right here
right now.
Every extra person
that we involve
increases the likelihood
that they know we're coming,
which increases the likelihood
that Christine and Callie
don't make it out of there.
That means no SWAT,
no Marshals, no backup.
It's just us.
I never meant for it
to go this way.
How did you mean it to go?
After 9/11, nobody cared about
drugs coming into this country.
So, to secure the borders,
we started to work
with the cartels.
And they kept us informed about
any terrorist activity
coming our way.
And it worked.
We haven't had an attack since.
We were protecting
this country.
You were killing cops
and getting rich
putting drugs
into this country.
Rita.
That's why you killed Howard.
He was onto you.
You wanted to cover
your tracks.
No. That was McGrath.
He's out of control.
Rita, just take a second.
I never meant for any of this
to go this way.
I guess I just need to know
if it was ever real.
It was always real.
I panicked.
I lost control.
Did you love me?
Yes.
I swear.
Well, that means...
We're good. We got it.
99% voice match.
...absolutely nothing to me,
you piece of shit.
Hey. It's me.
What the hell's going on?
You screwed up
is what's going on.
We've been compromised.
I'll explain when I get there.
We're moving the hostages.
Cuba, long-term hold...
...to keep Lowrey, Burnett
and Aretas quiet
while we sort this out.
I'm bringing a seaplane.
I'll be there at first light.
All right, pack this place up.
All equipment and personnel,
prepare to move.
We're moving the hostages
out of the country.
What happened to your hand?
They call that
a Colombian manicure.
What's so great about it
is it's the maximum amount
of pain, but you don't die.
So now you've decided to be
the one holding the pliers.
Everybody breaks.
Everyone.
Your husband is gonna
kneel down in front of me
and beg for your lives.
And then you're gonna
watch me kill him.
You don't know my husband.
Well, not officially, but...
I look forward
to seeing him again.
Mm-mm.
Come on, Mike.
Yeah.
That-that's enough, dawg.
That's enough.
Okay, well, we'll circle back
on that one.
All right, the plane is ready.
We roll in 20.
It's an
abandoned amusement park.
There should be no civilians.
Plane is gonna land
from the south
on the one side.
Marcus and I will be
on the plane.
Armando's gonna make his way
in the water-- the two side.
Kelly, Rita, this road is
one way in, one way out.
You're holding that road.
Dorn, you're gonna
control the air.
Drones in the air.
Jamming is active.
Comms are secure.
As far as they know, Lockwood
is on his way with the plane
to move the hostages to Cuba.
The second they get close
to the plane with the hostages,
it's quick kills.
Neutralize all threats.
These motherfuckers killed
a lot of good cops.
They have my wife.
They have Callie.
They attacked our families.
We're not losing today.
Hey.
We get on the ground,
you even flinch,
you'll be dead in .24 seconds.
I concur.
I got one lookout
on the platform outside.
I got one sniper
on the roof of building two.
Tee those up.
Everybody, keep moving.
-What are those?
-Gators.
I thought it was
an abandoned gator park.
Abandoned by humans.
It's actually
an old amusement park.
It sat on ten acres.
Abandoned in 2017
after Hurricane Irma.
Their main attraction was
an albino alligator named Duke,
who was 16 feet long,
900 pounds.
"And legend has it
he's still there"?
Fuck that.
Armando's at his QTH.
Hostages are coming out now.
McGrath plus three.
Everybody, stay calm.
All right.
Mike.
Mike, do you have the shot?
Negative. I do not have a shot.
I do not have a shot.
-Mike, he's right there.
-I don't have it.
I don't have it.
They stopped. Why'd they stop?
Shit.
Let's go.
Armando,
they're closing in on you.
-Do they see him?
-I don't know.
Mike, now. Your chance is now.
They can see him.
They know we're here.
I don't have it.
Negative. Negative. Negative.
You got to take
the fucking shot.
Armando's burnt.
Shit.
Full green! Engage!
Kelly, get us there.
Go, go, go!
Contact, west dock side.
Sh...
-Dorn, take out that sniper!
-Shit.
Sending the drone.
Got him.
Not now, Mike!
Not now!
It's okay.
Not your fault.
Cut that
bitch-ass shit out, Mike!
I need Nasty Mike. Nasty Mike!
Bad shit happens, but
that doesn't mean you're bad.
Do that donkey shit, a'ight?
That's what I'm talking about.
That shit right there.
That's that shit right there.
Bad boy! Bad boy!
Bad Boy Mike! All right?
Mike!
Dorn, take out
the vehicles on the four side.
Copy.
Go! Go! Move!
Sir! We're taking heavies.
We lost the trucks
and three guys outside.
Goddamn it!
Set firing positions,
both sides.
-Let 'em in.
-Go.
Marshal Howard, heat signature
at the site of the AMMO van
is showing explosions.
ETA 15 minutes.
Dorn, we need cover, and
we need eyes inside. Go now.
Here comes the smoke.
I got your six.
-Move, move, move!
-Eyes up!
Oh, shit!
It's like
redneck Jurassic Park in here.
Let's get out of here now.
Kelly, go.
Dorn, back up Kelly inside.
I'm going after Lockwood.
Babe, I'm coming.
Armando, go for Callie!
Let go!
Mike!
Marcus!
Go!
I'm out!
Nice to meet you, Mr. Lowrey.
Grenade!
Holy shit!
Hang on!
Stop!
Christine!
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Mike, I got this!
-No. No, no.
-Here I come, baby!
-Here I come!
-No, no, no!
Marcus!
-What?
-Behind you.
Oh, shit.
I got this, Mike.
It's just Dukey, baby.
Marcus, my gun.
I dropped my gun in the water.
-It's by your foot.
-I don't need no gun, Mike.
Begone, gator.
This is not your place, Duke.
I rebuke you.
See, Mike?
That's how you command
the universe.
-Oh, shit!
-The gun. Where's the gun?
Go, go, go, go.
That motherfucker racist, Mike.
-Go. Go.
-That motherfucker racist.
Mike sent me.
I need you to trust me.
Run. Run!
Come on. Come on. Get up.
No!
Go. I'll slow you down.
Eyes on location.
Oh, shit.
You alive?
Shit. Okay. Hey.
Rita, stop this.
You don't want to shoot me.
You're right.
-Ow! Ow.
-Come here.
-Okay, okay. It's okay.
-Ow.
-I fucking hate politicians.
-Shh.
-Let's move!
-Go, go!
Okay. Okay, here.
-Put me down.
-Okay.
-It's okay.
-You okay?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Okay.
Hey.
Thank you.
I've been here before.
Oh, shit.
How did you let him catch you?
He's sneaky as hell, Mike.
Your wife and I
were having a debate.
She seems to have
an inflated impression of you.
-Mike.
-Hey, bae.
Nevertheless, this is
the end of the road.
One of them is about to die.
You choose.
What you don't know,
Mr. McGrath,
is one of 'em can't die.
Who you talking 'bout?
A wise man told me I was gonna
have to make a hard choice.
You need to check
with that motherfucker
before you out here
choosing shit.
You have
five seconds, Mr. Lowrey.
We gonna need
some more time, sir.
Four, three...
Mike, don't you do
no dumb shit.
...two...
-Mike. Mike.
-Hey. Hey. I'm here.
Motherfucker done shot me.
-Oh, damn.
-Here.
-No, Mike.
-Okay. Just let me check it.
-Let me see.
-Your donkey ass shot me again.
-Let me look at it. Just...
-Don't touch me
with your donkey hooves, Mike.
-Just... Look, what you...
-Damn, man.
Listen, I had to fucking
take the shot.
-No, Mike. No.
-Marcus.
Let me take a look, Marcus.
You see that shit, Christine?
Look, I shot you in your vest.
-Stop bitching.
-It don't matter, okay?
You see what you done devoted
your life to, Christine?
I've got eyes on Aretas.
-Moving in.
-Shit. That's Judy.
Armando, do you copy?
Shit.
Mom!
Mom, don't.
Get away from her.
-Mom.
-Now!
Mom, listen to me.
You don't understand.
Callie, I need you
to listen to me.
I want you to step slowly
to your right
and walk towards me.
Mom, Mom, I'm fine, okay?
Callie, I need you
to move out of the way.
Mom.
Mom, don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Mom, he saved me. Stop!
Judy! Judy!
-Back off, Mike!
-Judy. Judy.
Put the gun down!
He saved my life.
Please, Mom.
Are you hit? Are you hit?
I'm good.
You good?
You did good. You did good.
Howard, where are you?
Howard, do you copy?
Howard, what's your location?
Go.
Before I change my mind.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Here. You good? You good?
Hey. Take this.
Head south.
-Don't look back.
-Hey.
I got it.
Be good.
It's not up to you, Detective.
Come on, come on.
We got injured cops here.
And you, I need you
to bring the writ to me now.
I know, I know, I know.
-How is he?
-You know, pulling through.
Ow.
Don't kiss him, Christine.
Mike, in our next life,
you coming back
as a pair of my shoes.
And I ain't gonna wear
no socks,
and I'm-a step
in all kind of shit.
Miami DA and mayoral candidate
Adam Lockwood and former
Army Ranger James McGrath
were killed this morning in a
firefight in the Florida Keys.
It is believed
that Lockwood and McGrath were
the key links between Miami
law enforcement and cartels...
The late Captain Howard
has been fully exonerated.
Coconspirators are
currently being rounded up
by the FBI and the Miami PD.
The search for convicted killer
Armando Aretas continues.
The fugitive remains at large.
-Hey, hey, hey.
-Hey.
-My people.
-Where's Theresa?
She's with Little Marcus
by the swings.
Hey. I'm about
to hook y'all up.
-I'm about to hook you up.
-Please. We're starving.
Watch this.
Partner.
What's all this?
What...
Why you got on an apron?
Work on my grill skills.
No, Mike,
you got to earn the grill.
This takes seasonings
and temperatures.
You can't just be cooking
on my grill.
Your grill?
Joker, this is a public park.
You don't own
every grill you see.
You know what, Mike?
Why don't you go make some
potato salad and set the table.
Oh, you talking dirty.
Now, look, I-I don't know
what you got going on
with your barbecue dictatorship
in your mind,
but I ain't the one.
I'm cooking on this grill
whether you like it or not.
-Hey, Mike...
-Excuse me, sirs.
You're not...
Why you...
What you doing, Reggie?
Request permission
to cook my chicken.
Permission denied, Reggie.
Go ahead somewhere, man.
Take your smock off
and go play with the kids.
Listen, this is the...
this is the man area
of the-the barbecue.
-Yeah.
-Look, you know what?
All due respect, we appreciate
that you did save people
that we love.
-We appreciate that, right?
-Yeah, we appreciate that.
-We appreciate that
from here, Reggie. -Yeah.
-Now, back the fuck up.
-Yeah.
All right, look, I'm-I'm
willing to compromise with you.
You can work that half
of the grill-- it's small--
and I'll work this half, but...
Is he still standing there?
Yes, he is.
Huh. That's weird.
Yeah.
He think he hard now.
You need to let
that motherfucker know
he ain't cooking no chicken
out here today.
Mike, he killed 15 people
at the house.
So you not gonna handle
this shit?
Yeah, I'm gonna let that
motherfucker cook the chicken.
Yeah, there's something weird
in his eyes.
Uh, so I'm-a make
the potato salad.
-I'm-a set the table.
-Yeah.
Permission granted, Reggie.
There you go.
Come on.
Bring your ass on.
It's too hot out here
for this shit.
Wish I had a horse.
At least I could ride
that motherfucker.
All this free air out here,
and I still smell
your stinking ass.
I curse you, donkey.
I curse you for all lifetimes.
Oh!
You mother--
Fuck you, Marcus.